(Howard:)Did you send everyone to
the principal's office already?
(Sheldon:)No one signed up.
(Leonard:)Well, that's not your fault.
(Sheldon:)I called the department
secretary to see what happened.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, I have a reputation
for being obnoxious.
(Leonard:)What?
(Raj:)Hey, Sheldon, I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)No, it's fine.
(Sheldon:)Now I can devote all my time
to dark matter.
(Raj:)Aw, you brought cookies
for everyone?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. Fig Newtons.
I was going to ask them:
which scientist both helped
(Sheldon:)to develop calculus and had
a famous cookie named after him?
(Sheldon:)And then after
someone said "Newton,"
(Sheldon:)I was going to tell them
they're wrong.
(Sheldon:)The cookies are named
after a town in Massachusetts.
(Sheldon:)And then I'd throw
the cookies away.
(Howard:)Hey, what if I took your class?
(Sheldon:)Why would you do that?
(Leonard:)Yeah, why would you do that?
What's wrong with you?